gleba.pl 2018-06-25

# Privacy policy and usage of cookies

Privacy policy and usage of cookies

Respecting the privacy of Users of our websites, we follow the Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy defines the rules of processing and protection of personal data obtained from Users when they use the AfterMarket.pl website hosted at the web address: _www.aftermarket.pl_ , (hereinafter “the Website”), made available by MICHAU ENTERPRISES LIMITED with its registered office at the following address: Chytron, 26 Street, Office 21 P.C. 1075 Nicosia, Cyprus, entered into the Registry of Companies kept by the Minister of Trade, Industry and Tourism, under number HA 245422

Within the Privacy Policy, “the User” means a natural person making use of the Website.

Privacy Policy.aking use of the Website is tantamount to giving consent to the following rules, terms and conditions set out in this 

**Personal Data**

According to the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data (“Regulation”), MICHAU ENTERPRISES LIMITED, with its address in Cyprus at Chytron 3, Office 301, P.C. 1075 Nicosia, entered into the Registry of Companies kept by the Minister of Trade, Industry and Tourism, under number HA 245422 (hereinafter referred to as  “AM”), informs that they are the administrator of personal data provided by the User in connection with or during the use of the Website. Personal data is processed pursuant to the Regulation, and in cases required thereunder, with the consent by the User.

AM collects only the data that is necessary to conclude an agreement and to provide the service chosen by the User, to answer questions asked to AM, to market its own services, to provide information on their offers.

At the time of registering or ordering a service, AM collects the information provided by the User in the available forms. This data includes:

  1. surname and first name,
  2. e-mail address,
  3. address of residence,
  4. address for correspondence,
  5. phone number,
  6. payment data (including bank account number and hashed credit card number).

In the cases required by the provisions of the Regulation, the User's consent to processing their personal data is given in the electronic form by ticking the appropriate box during the registration or other procedure with the purpose to enable the use of the Website. The User may revoke their consent to the processing of personal data at any time.

It is voluntary to provide the information marked as required on the Website, however doing so is necessary to conclude the agreement and for us to provide services for the User or to register the User on the Website. If the User does not make the required personal data available, it will not be possible to register the User on the Website or to conclude a contract and provide services for the User.

The ground for AM to process personal data provided by the User is the need to perform the agreement and, at the User’s request, to take the necessary actions prior to its conclusion (art. 6 par. 1 point b) of the Regulation). For the marketing of our own services and AM’s sending information on their offer to the e-mail address provided by the User, the ground for processing of User’s personal data is the pursuance of the legitimate interest of AM (art. 6 par. 1 point f) of the Regulation). AM processes data to provide information about their products and services and thereby makes it possible to send information about the current offer to the User. In the case of providing the Newsletter service for the User’s benefit, the ground for processing of data is the User consent (art. 6 par. 1 point b) of the Regulation), which the User may revoke at any time.

User’s personal data will be stored in a form allowing for identification of the User for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data are collected and lawfully processed. Therefore, personal data will be stored for the period necessary to perform the contract and to provide the service chosen by the User. After that time, data will be processed for the period necessary to resolve any potential disputes that may arise in connection with the services being provided, e.g. relating to claims (the period shall include the period of limitation of claims under the contract, in accordance with the provisions in force).

**Entrusting personal data**

The processing of the User’s personal data or other data referred to in the Privacy Policy may be entrusted, on the basis of a written agreement concluded pursuant to the Regulation, to entities that provide AM services, e.g. hosting, administration, maintenance and management of the Website.

AM entrusts, on the basis of a written agreement concluded pursuant to the Regulation, the processing of the User’s personal data or other data referred to in the Privacy Policy to other entities that provide AM services directly, to the extent necessary to fulfil orders made through the Website. In the case of User making electronic payments or paying by card, the Administrator may make User’s data available to a selected entity processing the above payments on the Website.

Subject to the above-mentioned provisions, personal data collected will not be disclosed to any other persons or institutions, unless it is required by provisions of applicable law in force, or it is necessary for the purpose of processing personal data and an appropriate agreement ensuring the protection of rights and privacy of the User is concluded.

**User’s rights and obligations**

The User has the right to access the content of their personal data and the right to demand that the personal data be supplemented, updated, transferred, their processing be limited, rectified, temporarily or permanently withheld from processing or deleted when data are incomplete, outdated, untrue or have been collected in breach of the law or if they are no longer necessary for the purpose for which they were collected.

In the case of processing the User’s data for the purpose of marketing a service and own products, the User may at any time make a written and justified request not to process their data because of their particular situation or to object to the processing of their data for that purpose.

AM makes it possible for the User to delete their personal data from the data set at User’s request or pursuant to the Regulation.

AM may refuse to delete personal data if the User has violated the rules of the Website or the legal provisions in force, and it is necessary to retain the personal data in order to explain the circumstances of the breach and determine the User’s liability.

If the User posts on the Website any personal data of other people (including their first name and surname, address, phone number or e-mail address), they are allowed to do so only on condition that applicable law be not infringed and these people’s personal rights be not violated.

**Additional information on cookies:**

Cookies are text files that are stored on User’s terminal device’s hard drive and are used to recognize User’s device while reconnecting to an Internet site that uses cookies.

Cookies are not used to determine User's identity, but they allow more accurate identification of personal needs of the User who handles the device and thereby allow offering them services that are better and more tailored to their demands and facilitating connection to websites of interest.

Cookies are used by AM also for:

  * statistics – allowing to create, for the company’s  and contractors’ needs, statistics of websites’ functioning and Users’ visits,
  * presentation and customization of marketing messages displayed on given terminal device.

The User may refuse to consent for placing cookies on their terminal device. To do this, the User should use the option that disables the downloading and storing cookies in their web browser. The web browser provider ensures the method of disabling the download and storing of cookies in popular web browsers.

Deleting cookies may result in the loss of ability to take advantage of certain features of AM websites.

**Other data**

In some cases, AM automatically collects certain types of information when the User visits the Website or by means of electronic mail addresses. Such operational data related to the use of the Website (IP address, domain name, web beacons) are stored in aggregated and anonymized form and are not made available to third parties. These data are used to better understand and to streamline the operation, functionality, and performance of the Website and generate statistics supporting the administration of the Website.

Users' personal data are also processed by AM for the purpose of automated profiling. Profiling takes place when AM processes personal data in an automated manner by using Users' personal data to evaluate certain personal factors, in particular, to analyze or forecast Users' preferences, credibility, behavior and location. Every User has the right to object to AM profiling if they find that the profiling violates their rights and freedoms unless the data administrator (controller) proves that his own interests take precedence over those of the individual. The Customer may express their objection to profiling free of charge in any form via the available channels of communication with AM.

**Data protective measures**

User’s personal data is secured against being made available to unauthorized persons, being taken over by an unauthorized person, processed in breach of the applicable provisions and modified, lost, damaged or destroyed. This is achieved by taking technical and organizational measures to ensure that the personal data processed is protected in a way, which is appropriate to the risks and categories of data being protected.

In particular, the Administrator uses technical measures to prevent the acquisition or modification of data by unauthorized persons. The Administrator protects the data sets against the access by unauthorized entities, provides access to the User's account only after authentication, including entering the personal login and password. Moreover, the data provided by the User during the process of filling in and sending Internet forms are encrypted by using SSL certificates.

**Contact**

The User of the Website may at any time contact AM to obtain information on whether and how AM uses or intends to use their personal information and to report any events affecting the security of information and its transfer. Address, at which User may contact AM: _kontakt@aftermarket.pl_.

**Variation to the Privacy Policy**

AM reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy and, at the same time, warrants that User rights hereunder will not be limited without User’s consent. Any variations to the Privacy Policy will be published on the website: _www.aftermarket.pl_.

**How to contact the supervisory authority**

In all matters relating to the processing of User’s personal data and the application and implementation of this Privacy Policy, the User has the right to file a complaint with the President of the Office for the Protection of Personal Data.
